Is this your Lamborghini?
It is my Lamborghini.
And what do you do for a living
to be able to afford a Lamborghini out in Dallas?
I am a professional athlete.
I play in the NFL.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
38 in one year.
$38 million.
Is this your G-Wagon though?
Yeah.
And what do you do for a living?
You're gonna go right into it anyway,
so he's good, he's good.
What do you do for a living?
I work for a private equity company.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
About 10 million something.
$10 million.
And how long have you been a business owner for?
About 18 years now.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, I have as a matter of fact.
Yeah.
Yeah, there was a time
where I worked in a store
and I didn't have enough food to eat.
So when no one was in the break room,
I went in the refrigerator
and I took a little
bit out of everybody else's lunch,
just enough so that they wouldn't notice,
but enough so that I would have something to eat.
How can somebody become a millionaire in 2024?
Highland Park in Dallas, Texas
is the number six wealthiest city
in the entire United States.
And if you've ever been to Dallas,
you never know who you're gonna run into
out here.
And today I'm gonna be going all over Highland Park
asking multi-millionaires
what they did for a living to become millionaires
and how you can start your path
to becoming financially free in 2024.
So with that being said,
let's get this video on the way.
Is this your Lamborghini?
It is my Lamborghini.
And what do you do for a living
to be able to afford a Lamborghini out in Dallas?
I'm retired.
What did you do?
What industry did you pursue a career in?
Supply chain.
Were you a business owner?
I was a business owner.
And how long were you an entrepreneur for?
40 years.
Over those 40 years,
what's the greatest lesson about entrepreneurship
you learned that you pass on to someone
about to start their first business?
Tell the truth.
How important is it to keep your word in business?
You don't keep your word in business,
you have no business.
And what was your secret to sales, right?
Selling in a competitive industry like supply chain.
Be honest.
This isn't my only Lamborghini.
I have three.
You have three?
I guess over these 40 years,
what was the most amount of money
that your business generated?
A lot.
Could you give me a range?
Eight figures?
Yeah.
What was the best financial advice
that you would see from a mentor?
You follow me into this space and I'll tell you.
I'll tell you two things.
The first one is be an expert
about what you're talking about.
Don't be a fool who listens to internet.
Do your research, do your homework,
and know more than anybody else knows.
And you can build an incredible career
on very little money,
because I did it twice.
Now, what was your secret to scaling, right?
How did you take your business
from seven to eight figures?
Finding a way to manage money.
Don't be the bank.
And have you ever been broke before?
Twice.
What was the turning point like for you?
How did you escape poverty
and how did you break that cycle?
Be tougher than poverty.
One last one for you.
And be hungry.
How old are you now?
What's one lesson about business
you would give to somebody
that they won't learn in business school?
Standing out is the most important thing.
AI is going to replace commonality.
You got to use your brain.
You got to be creative.
You got to be inventive.
You got to find another angle in.
Don't do the same things.
I love it, man.
See you, man.
Thank you so much.
Really appreciate you.
All I'm going to say is
that's got to be one of the craziest experiences
that I've ever had running this channel.
My guy was,
we went up to him in the Lamborghini
and he said,
if you want to ask me questions,
you got to ask him right here.
He ended up wanting to do the interview
and he just dropped some amazing value
and advice for everybody out there.
I love that he said,
keep your word.
If you don't have your word,
you have nothing in this world of business.
Great interview, man.
Let's go get this next one, man.
Dallas is going to go crazy.
Is it cool if I ask you a few questions
for the channel?
I would love to, man,
but I have an appointment
I got to go into before.
Is this your G-Wagon though?
Yeah.
And what do you do for a living?
You're going to go right into it anyway.
So he's good.
He's good.
What do you do for a living?
I work for a private equity company.
What does it take to stand out
in the business world today?
Seem with a couple of pieces of advice
and then that's it, man.
Nothing comes easy.
Yeah.
Nothing comes overnight.
Be patient.
How important was that delayed gratification
for you, man?
A lot of people, they want it instantly.
They want to get rich quick.
You got to trust your path.
Like I said, nothing happens easy.
I think the problem today
is when I see young guys
getting to finance,
everyone expects to have something overnight, right?
That doesn't come that way.
As somebody in private equity,
when it comes to the way
that people look at money,
what's the number one thing
in your opinion
that separates the middle class
from those who end up
building that long-term wealth
like yourself?
I think people today
buy things that they can't afford.
I mean, look at Instagram, for example.
I mean, it's good for the platform
you guys are doing,
but I think in today's world,
everyone sees things
that they don't necessarily know
the truth of everyone's situation
and they expect that
whatever they see
is how they need to be living.
You live your own life.
For instance, this year I started,
I got off all social media.
So I won't even see this interview
unless someone sends it to me.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
If this is going public,
I don't want to answer that.
You're saying just like a range maybe?
Or like seven figures, eight figures?
Yeah, seven, seven.
You're in private equity.
What's the best industry
people should be looking
to get into right now?
You're in the money business.
I think everybody's looking
for a get rich quick scheme nowadays.
You know, just go to school,
learn from somebody.
It all ties together, right?
Go learn from somebody that's done it,
but understand that while you're learning,
you're not going to make
what that person has
and then take that knowledge
and go do it.
But I do got to run now.
You're a very good interviewer, man.
Thank you.
Appreciate you, man.
Have a good one, bro.
I appreciate you.
Good, man.
You're relentless.
Yes, sir.
I appreciate you.
So we just put up on my guy
coming out of the G-Wagon,
heading to a meeting.
And find experts.
Find the most successful people
that you can.
Learn everything you can from them.
Go apply and execute.
And what did he say?
In order to build something great,
in order to do great things,
it's not going to happen overnight.
It's going to take time.
Great things take sacrifice
and they take time as well.
Great interview, man.
Let's go get this next one.
I go all over the country,
but I'm based in Austin.
Just asking people
a few questions
on the best advice
to the younger generation
and kids coming out of school.
Love to ask you some
people questions for the G-Wagon.
Is that cool?
Really cool.
What industry did you decide
to pursue a career in?
Restaurant business.
You're a business owner?
Yes, sir.
And how long have you been
a business owner for?
About 10 years.
And how many restaurants
do you own?
Five.
What's the most amount of money
that you've ever made
in a single year?
About 10 million something.
10 million dollars.
And how did you scale
your business from...
If I tell you in what,
it's just in tacos.
Tacos is really big.
You said tacos?
Yes, sir.
Tacos, yes, sir.
That's what we do.
We not even have
like big restaurants.
You should come to my business
and you're going to be
what we do.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes, sir.
I used to sleep
in the...
In the parking lots.
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
What was that turning point
like for you?
Like how did you know
you wanted to get really serious
about becoming financially free?
Well, I think what you broke
can make you think different,
you know?
Why?
Because what are you going to lose?
Like me, I was not going to lose
anything if I tried whatever.
You know what I mean?
I was already...
I was already in the ground.
So, what else?
Right.
It's just...
Whatever you do,
you just go forward.
You know what I mean?
For somebody who may be
at rock bottom right now,
what's an actionable step
that they can really take
to get their life back on track?
Well, the first thing is
you need to have
God in your heart.
I think it's really important
and I know maybe
it sounds kind of crazy,
but you got to have
God in your heart.
And whenever you have
God in your heart,
everything is going to come
to your life by their self.
Be honest with you.
Because I've been in the streets
and nothing,
nothing was happening.
So, as soon as I put
God in my heart,
it's when I see the difference.
Now, how do you stand out
in business, right?
Like a lot of people,
there's a lot of restaurants,
a lot of people selling food, right?
Let me tell you
by my story.
My wife and I,
we start inside
of the gas station.
It would just hurt me
and one guy.
And then from there,
we just start.
To today,
we have five locations
and I have, I think,
between 85 to 100 employees.
So, like I'm saying,
you just got to push hard
and then everything
is going to happen
by their self.
Did you go to college?
No, sir.
Why not?
I don't know if you want
to say that, but...
Yeah, go for it.
Say it.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Well, I have a different
opinion for a school,
but especially, like,
if you really want
to be a business guy,
I think it's not school
to teach you business.
I met a guy
who was a teacher
for, I think,
30 to 40 years
and he never
had a business.
How are you going
to be teaching me,
like my teacher,
you never have a business?
You know?
Yeah.
So, my kids want to
be in school for business
and I was like,
if you really want
to be a business guy,
you got to be on my side.
You got to wake up early.
No matter how much
money you have,
it doesn't matter
how many businesses
you have,
you still need to work hard.
Appreciate you, man.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
Appreciate you, man.
So, I work as
a security for his property.
This is private property.
Management has asked
that we stop doing
areas and just leave.
All right, you guys.
So, we had just finished
up that last interview
with my guy that did
$10 million across
his restaurant businesses
and they just told us
to leave, man.
Otherwise, they may
have to charge us
with criminal trespassing
but all I got to say is
they don't know the
mission behind this channel
and we're trying to
bring you guys
some of the best advice
from some of the most
successful people
in the entire world.
So, by any means necessary,
we're going to keep
this video going
in Highland Park, man.
We're going to have
to be careful.
It's not going to be easy now
but all I got to say
is some of the best advice
that I ever got
that I'm going to give to you
is take the risk
or lose the chance.
We're not going anywhere.
Let's keep this video going.
Come on, man.
What industry did you
decide to pursue a career in?
How do I explain this?
I'm a pro athlete.
All I've ever wanted to do
in my whole entire life
is be a pro athlete
and I'll play for the
Buffalo Bills.
Throughout your career,
what has been the most
amount of money
that you've ever made
in a single year?
I got my baby mama
over there.
Let me see.
$38 million in one year.
$38 million.
That is incredible.
Let me ask you this.
What's been the best
financial advice
that you've ever received
throughout your career?
Save bread.
I'm a huge proponent
of just saving bread
until the timing is right.
The trick is
to make it sustainable
over a long period of time.
Mike Tyson went through
$400 million.
You hear these horror stories
all the time.
What are you doing
to preserve that wealth?
Save bread.
Don't spend it.
It's Valentine's Day
so we're just spending
a little bread today.
Save bread.
Hold on to it
and just wait
for the right circumstances.
Of course,
you've got to have
the financial education
and at the same time
save bread until you get it.
You made it to the NFL,
the National Football
League.
One of the highest honors
in all of sports.
99.9% of people
that pick up a football
don't ever make it
to that professional level.
What was it that you did
that separated you
and enabled you
to get to the
National Football League?
I think I always
possessed the ability
to evolve.
It was always people
that was better than me.
that were stronger, faster.
I just was resilient
and I think still to this day
I still possess that quality
just resiliency
and I think that carries me
in my professional career
and in my personal life as well.
You've had longevity
I'd say over 10 years now
in the National Football League.
It seems like 14 years.
A lot of people
maybe they'll stay in
for 2-3 years.
What was the secret
to that longevity
being able to stay in
the game for that long?
It's a little bit
of God's grace too.
I can't sit here
and say that I did this
all on my own.
There's a lot of stuff
that divine intervention
just got me in
and got me out
of a lot of stuff
and kept me healthy.
But at the same time
my job is to make sure
my body's ready to go
and not only physically
but mentally.
I'm a huge proponent
of mental health
and self-awareness
and I think all of those
things have been tools
to get me where I'm at today.
Awesome man.
Appreciate you man.
All right you guys
so we just interviewed
Von Miller.
For those of you
who don't know
that is one of the
greatest linebackers
of all time.
He's one of the best
football players
that's ever played
in the NFL
and he made $38 million
in a single year
and what did he say
was the best financial
advice that he ever
received was to save bread.
A lot of people
they'll sign massive
contracts and they'll
go broke because
they don't know
what to do with that money.
So not only do you
have to save it
but you got to make
it work for you man.
Great interview.
Shout out to Von.
Shout out to Dallas.
This video just keeps
getting even more insane.
Let's go get this
next interview man.
Come on guys.
How long have you
been a business owner for?
Oh let's see
about 18 years now.
What has been the
most amount of money
that you've ever made
in a single year?
Half a million.
And that's for yourself.
And that's just me.
Have you ever been
broke before?
Yeah I have as a matter
of fact.
Yeah.
Yeah there was a time
where I worked in a store
and I didn't have
enough food to eat
so when no one
was in the break room
I went in the refrigerator
and I took a little bit
out of everybody
else's lunch
just enough so that
they wouldn't notice
but enough so that
I would have something
to eat.
What was that turning
point like for you?
How did you know
that you wanted to
get really serious
about becoming
financially free
and starting to build
that wealth?
What was the
turning point like?
That's a good question.
I would have to say
I had a lot of
older friends growing up
and I watched them
really closely
and a lot of times
I would I guess
just be envious
of what they were doing
but still scared
of taking the chances
that they were taking
but that's the only
way you do it.
How old are you now?
I am 63.
How important is it
to take a risk
at an early age?
Oh it's very important.
I think the biggest
risks that you take
early on are the ones
that are really
going to pay off
and really nobody
really meets their
full potential
unless they take
risks early on.
Now let me ask you
what was the biggest
risk that you took
throughout your career?
I think stepping
out on my own
and not being content
with a paycheck
from a big company
and working really hard
just so that they
could succeed.
I think the biggest
risk I've taken
is taking all the
nervousness that I had
about it and just said
nope we're doing it
or we'll regret it
the rest of our lives.
How can somebody
become a millionaire
in 2024?
Really be willing
to make sacrifices
work hard
don't show off
be honest
I think honesty
is the biggest thing
and don't be afraid
to reach out to people
also.
I think the people
that I have seen
that have really
struggled the most
are the people
that are afraid
to pick up a phone
or to call on somebody
that they've worked
with in the past
and get advice from them
or get some kind
of support from them.
Thank you so much
for your time sir
I really appreciate that.
Thank you very much.
You got great advice
really appreciate you.
Man you guys
this has got to be
one of the wildest
videos that we've ever
done at the School
of Hard Knocks.
Dallas, Texas is crazy.
You never know
who you're going
to run into out there
but I want you to
like and subscribe
for amazing content
on the way coming
very soon because
we're on a mission
to bring you guys
the best advice
from some of the
most successful
entrepreneurs and
business owners
in the entire world
and I have a very
special announcement
to make.
We just launched
the Hard Knocks
newsletter where
we're going to be
sending out weekly
updates, insights
and lessons from
the world's top
entrepreneurs in
every industry.
You're not going
to want to miss it
so subscribe now
the link is in the
description below
go subscribe to
the Hard Knocks
newsletter.
With that being said
we'll see you guys
in the next video
click here to watch
our full version
of the Hard Knocks
video going all
over Miami asking
luxury yacht owners
how they became
wealthy and how
you can start your
path to becoming
financially free in